agarwalpackers.com 2014-06-25

# Agarwal Packers and Movers Privacy Policy

| [Home](http://www.agarwalpackers.com/) |  | Profile |  | Why Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd. |  | Services |  | Strength |  | Agarwal Movers Group |  | Contact Us |  | Site Map |   
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
Our USP |  | Advantages |  | Shifting Process |  | Locations |  | International Moving |  | Storage Capacity |  | Safety Features |  | Career  
---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---|---  
  
**[Home](http://www.agarwalpackers.com/)** » Privacy Policy

**The short version:**

Agarwal Packers and Movers Ltd does not rent, sell, or give out your information to anyone outside of Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd. or its authorized agents. Only Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd. or an agent working on behalf of Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd. may have access to information gathered through this web site. Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd. uses this information to provide services tailored to the interests of our users. One of the uses of your information may be for mailing purposes. You may request at any time to be removed from our mailing list or email list by using the procedures described below.

You can visit most of our website without having to give any information about yourself. The full text of our Privacy Policy is below: 

**Full text version:**

Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd. has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for all domains owned by Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd.

**Information Collection and Use**

Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd. is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd. collects information from our users at several different points on our website. The purpose of this information is outlined on the page where this information is collected. Information collected via this website is used to provide the services offered on that area of the site.

**Security**

In Services of our site where sensitive information may be transferred, all transmissions between client and server are encrypted using the industry standard SSL protocol. We also restrict the level of access our employees have to user information based on their responsibilities and hold them to high levels of confidentiality. 

**Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd uses cookies for security, session continuity, and customization purposes. If a user rejects a cookie, he/she may still use most of the Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd, but may not be able to gain access to some Services or use some features of the site.

**Log Files**

Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd uses client IP addresses to analyze site usage trends, administer the site, track users' movements within the Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.

**Links to other sites**

This site contains links to other sites. Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd. is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such web sites.

Mail your request to Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd, Agarwal Floor, Local Shopping Center, Sharda Niketan, Opp. Crescent Public School, Pitampura, New Delhi-110034

**Contacting the web site administrators**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this web site, please contact:

**Corporate office**  
**Agarwal Packers & Movers Ltd.**  
**Address :** Agarwal Floor, Local 

Shopping Center, Sharda Niketan, 

Opp. Crescent Public School, Pitampura, 

New Delhi-110034 - **(India)**  
**Phone :** +(91)-(11)-45004300  
**Fax :** +(91)-(11)-45063710  
**E-Mail :** [info@agarwalpackers.com](mailto:info@agarwalpackers.com?subject=Agarwal%20Packers%20&%20Movers%20Mail%20Through%20agarwalpackers.com)

Packers & Movers Agra  
Packers & Movers Ambala  
Packers & Movers Allahabad  
Packers & Movers Aurangabad  
Packers & Movers Ahmedabad   
Packers & Movers Ankleshwar  
Packers & Movers Banaras  
Packers & Movers Bhopal  
Packers & Movers Baroda  
Packers & Movers Bangalore  
Packers & Movers  
     Bhubaneswar  
Packers & Movers Bhuj  
Packers & Movers Chandigarh  
Packers & Movers Cuttack  

| 

Packers & Movers Coimbatore  
Packers & Movers Calicut  
Packers & Movers Cochin  
Packers & Movers Chennai  
Packers & Movers Dehradun  
Packers & Movers Delhi  
Packers & Movers Erode  
Packers & Movers Faridabad  
Packers & Movers Goa  
Packers & Movers Gurgaon  
Packers & Movers Gwalior  
Packers & Movers Gandhidham  
Packers & Movers Ghaziabad  
Packers & Movers Guwahati  
Packers & Movers Haridwar  

| 

Packers & Movers Hisar  
Packers & Movers Hubli  
Packers & Movers Hyderabad  
Packers & Movers Indore   
Packers & Movers Jamshedpur   
Packers & Movers Jodhpur   
Packers & Movers Jaipur   
Packers & Movers Jammu   
Packers & Movers Kanpur  
Packers & Movers Kolkata  
Packers & Movers Kalighat  
Packers & Movers Kolhapur  
Packers & Movers Kottayam  
Packers & Movers Ludhiana  
Packers & Movers Lucknow

| 

Packers & Movers Meerut  
Packers & Movers Madurai  
Packers & Movers Mumbai  
Packers & Movers Mysore  
Packers & Movers Mangalore  
Packers & Movers Nagpur  
Packers & Movers Navi Mumbai  
Packers & Movers Nasik  
Packers & Movers Noida  
Packers & Movers Patna  
Packers & Movers Patalganga  
Packers & Movers Pondichery  
Packers & Movers Port Blair  
Packers & Movers Pune  
Packers & Movers Raipur  

| 

Packers & Movers Ranchi  
Packers & Movers Rajkot  
Packers & Movers Rourkela  
Packers & Movers Renkuoot  
Packers & Movers Rudrapur  
Packers & Movers Raigarh  
Packers & Movers Siliguri  
Packers & Movers Surat  
Packers & Movers Tirupur  
Packers & Movers Trivandrum   
Packers & Movers Trichy  
Packers & Movers Udaipur  
Packers & Movers Varanasi  
Packers & Movers Vapi  

---|---|---|---|---
